练习 6-8：保持舌头不动。你和我将把舌头牢牢
Exercise 6-8, hold your tongue. You and I are going to read with our tongues firmly
顶在上腭读。如果愿意，可以用舌尖在那里顶住一枚干净的一角硬币。
held at the roofs of our mouths. If you want, hold a clean dime there with the
这枚硬币会提醒你舌头什么时候掉下来，因为它会直接掉出来。
tongue's tip. The dime will let you know when you've dropped your tongue because it
不要用糖果；湿糖果有黏性，会自己粘在那里。
will fall out. Do not use candy. It will hold itself there since wet candy is
如果你愿意，也可以把舌头放在牙齿之间读，而不是
sticky. If you prefer, you can read with your tongue between your teeth instead of
标准的牙齿后方位置，并使用一面小镜子。记住，使用
the standard behind the teeth position and use a small mirror. Remember that with
这个技巧时，你实际上能看到舌头消失，L 音也会脱落。
this technique, you can actually see your tongue disappear. L sounds drop off. It's
当然，听起来会很可笑，而且没人会故意这样说，
going to sound ridiculous, of course, and nobody would ever intentionally sound like
但没人会听到你练习。你并不想听起来像这样。
this, but no one will hear you practice. You don't want to sound like this. Force
即使在这个舌位上，也要强迫舌头发出各种元音。开始吧。
your tongue to make all the various vowels in spite of its position. Let's go. Viva
Lofroa!